[Music]
Deep, today's hero stocks include two cash market
stocks. The first one is Net Web Technology,
whose numbers came out this weekend.
After the numbers, the stock is seeing some amazing action. It has
risen to 73. Its
operating profit has increased to 86. The margin has
increased by 1. There has been an increase of 70% in profits. On the
basis of that, Network Technology
seems to be coming into a strong segment. So today's
first hero is this one, and the second hero is this one. The stock is
also a hero, and our expert is also a hero.
Okay, mess doc.
Oho, where is he? Is mess doc okay? Yes, please show
Mehul ji. Both our expert and the
stock are heroes. Look, today's price is around 7. It is
in amazing action, around 6. It is empty, it needs an excuse, it needs a reason
to rise. Today
Mehul ji also recommended that the stock
seems to be taking a good bullish action.
Garden Ship Builder also got some orders, so
this entire area is looking quite strong.
Cochin Garden, Mejgaon. All this is a
great action here, but actually.  One stock
which has a big surprise movement
on the positive side is Deep. The numbers from ICICI Lombard are
not looking that good to you
and some brokerages have
also cut a few targets. CLSA has done it from 2000 to
1950. JP Morgan has done it
from 1820 to 1700. After that, the stock which is strong
seems to be short covering and the
numbers are
not that bad as compared to what the market had expected. So in a way, you
can say that its performance could have been bad today,
but no, the real hero is the one from whom
you do not expect, the one from whom you expect it to be
bad, but despite that, it does well. So,
if you are going to find a hero in futures trading today, then
ICICI Lombard
is today's hero and zero stock for you.